<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My though repository</title>
    <link>http://savithakj.github.io/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My though repository</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:56:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://savithakj.github.io/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Review. SLEUTH: Real-time Attack Scenario Reconstruction from COTS Audit Data</title>
      <link>http://savithakj.github.io/reviews/sleuth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:56:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://savithakj.github.io/reviews/sleuth/</guid>
      <description>Paper: SLEUTH: Real-time Attack Scenario Reconstruction from COTS Audit Data by Md Nahid Hossain, Sadegh M. Milajerdi, Junao Wang, Birhanu Eshete, Rigel Gjomemo, R. Sekar, Scott D. Stoller, and V.N. Venkatakrishnan The paper presents a system to track attacks and methods to reconstruction the attack in real time. This real-time attack detection and scenario reconstruction system is used as a forensic tool where all the event logs are stored and analyzed in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review. CryptDB - Processing Queries on an Encrypted Database</title>
      <link>http://savithakj.github.io/reviews/cryptodb-processing-queries-on-an-encrypted-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 04:56:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://savithakj.github.io/reviews/cryptodb-processing-queries-on-an-encrypted-database/</guid>
      <description>Paper: CryptDB - Processing Queries on an Encrypted Database by Raluca Ada Popa, Catherine M.S. Redfield, Nickolai Zeldovich, and Hari Balakrishnan The paper proposed the use of encrypted Database server where none of the data is stored in plain text. The paper initially describes the problems that occur due to passive DB server attacks when the System Administrators have access to confidential information and such threat models. CryptDB is ideal to be used in cases of passive database server attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>